老兄，这好畸形哦
Man,this is weird.
你知不知道 嘎吱上尉（麦片品牌）的眉毛长到了帽子上？
Ever realize Cap'n Crunch's eyebrows are on his hat?
那叫畸型？
That's what's weird?
乔伊，那家伙这样子已经四十年了
The man's been captain of a cereal for 40 years.
怎样？
What?
汤匙，你舔完放回去
The spoon! You licked and you put.
你舔完放回去
You licked and you put.
所以呢？
Yeah,so?
你看不出那很恶心吗？ 就像你用我的牙刷一样恶心
Don't you see how gross that is? It's like you using my toothbrush!
你用过我的牙刷？
You used my toothbrush?
那是因为 我用红的那只去通排水孔嘛
Only because I used the red one to unclog the drain.
红色是我的
Mine is the red one!
上帝啊，罐头一打开，虫子就满处爬了（一发不可收拾）
Oh,God! Can open. Worms everywhere!
为什么牙刷不能共用…
Why can't we use the same toothbrush...
…肥皂就可以共用？
... but we can use the same soap?
因为肥皂是肥皂，会自我清洁
Because soap is soap. It's self-cleaning.
好吧，下一次你洗澡的时候…
The next time you shower...
…想想我最后洗什么 而你最先洗什么
...think about the last thing I wash and the first thing you wash.
六人行 第2季 第16集 乔伊搬走了
The One Where Joey Moves Out
瞧你们打扮的
Look at you fancy lads!
有什么大事？
What's the occasion?
记得我的电视剧里那个演昏迷不醒的人吗？
You know that guy on my show that's in a coma?
他要请我吃饭
He's having a brunch.
就等你了 好的
Ready when you are.
真不敢相信 你们真的要去刺青了
I can't believe you're actually getting tattoos.
你们要去刺青？
You guys are getting tattoos?
对，不能告诉罗斯 我要给他一个惊喜
But you cannot tell Ross because I wanna surprise him.
好狂野哦，你们要刺什么？
Wow,this is wild! What are you gonna get?
我要刺一朵百合
I'm getting a lily.
因为我妈就叫莉莉（百合）
For my mom,because her name's Lily.
真幸运 她要是叫大污点怎么办？
That's lucky. What if her name was Big Ugly Splotch?
那你们要刺哪里？ 我想在我肩上
-Where you getting it? -On my shoulder.
什么？
What?
什么在你肩上？
What's on your shoulder?
瑕疵
A chip.
我有很严重的态度问题
I've got a big attitude problem.
是刺青，我要去刺青啦 刺青？
-A tattoo. I'm getting a tattoo. -A tattoo?
你为什么要那么做？
Why? Why would you wanna do that?
你不觉得那酷吗？
You don't think they're kind of cool?
不，抱歉，我不觉得
No. Sorry,I don't.
怎么会有人 花钱去搞个一辈子的伤痕？
Why would anyone pay someone to scar their body for life?
万一要是刺得不好呢？
What if it doesn't come out right?
那不是变成永远的 “我头发剪丑了”吗？
It's like having a bad haircut all the time.
大家为什么都瞪着我？
Why is everyone staring at me?
罗斯，过来签给爸的生日卡 理查随时会到
Sign this card for Dad. Richard will be here soon.
理查也要去参加派对？
Richard's going to the party too?
他是我父母最好的朋友 他必须去
He's my parents' best friend. He has to go.
那你打算 今天告诉他们你们的事吗？
So is today the day you'll tell them about you two?
对，我爸的生日 我决定送他中风当礼物
Yeah,for my dad's birthday,I decided to give him a stroke.
不，你应该告诉他们
No,I think you should tell them.
我还不知道他对我有多认真 在搞清楚之前，我什么也不说
I don't know how serious he is. Until I do,I won't say anything.
我不知道，我想他们不会介意
I don't think Mom and Dad would mind.
记得你九岁 理查三十岁的时候，爸常说…
Remember when you were 9 and Richard was 30,Dad said...
…“天啊 真希望他们在一起”
... "God,I hope they get together."
-你好 -我在违章停车
-Hello?.-I'm double-parked,
好的，快点，罗斯
Okay. Come on, Ross.
-再见 -再见
-Bye, you.-Bye.
再见
Bye, you.
我们走，我们走 等等 等等
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go.Okay, wait, wait.
-会顺利的 -你不紧张吗
-It's gonna be fine.-Are you not nervous?.
我很恐惧，这是件吸收性很强的外套
I'm terrified.This is just a very absorbent suit.
-可以进了吗 -是的
-Shall we? -Yes
你知道吗？
You know what?
罗斯，我们换位置 你来站中间
Ross,let's switch places. You get in the middle.
不，这看起来像 我们想隐瞒什么
This looks like we're trying to cover something up.
莫妮卡，就算你骑着他进去 他们也不会相信的
You could come in straddling him,they still wouldn't believe it.
我们来了
We're here!
孩子们 是孩子们
-Hi,kids! -The children!
生日快乐，爸爸 谢谢
-Happy birthday,Dad. -Thank you.
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
你们谢过柏克大夫 载你们来了吗？
So you kids thanked Dr. Burke for the ride?
妈，事实上 莫妮卡帮我们两个谢过了
Actually,Mom,I think Monica thanked him for the both of us.
你们搭火车来吗？
So you kids take the train in?
不，理查柏克载他们来的
No,Richard Burke gave them a ride.
谈到他呀…
Speaking of whom...
…听说 他在城里有个二十岁的年幼女友
... I hear he's got some 20-year-old twinkie in the city.
手指抽筋，抱歉
Finger cramp! Oh,God!
来，让我来，妈
Sorry. Here,let me get that,Mom.
理查在青少年部“购物”
So Richard's shopping in the junior section?
还在讲那个吗？
Are we still on that?
想也知道她的智商一定超低
You just know she's got the lQ of a napkin.
说不定连漂亮都谈不上
She's probably not even pretty.
只是够年轻 所以一切都还没下垂
Just young enough so that everything is still pointing up.
你相信这个地方吗？
Can you believe this place?
我知道，这个公寓很棒
I know. This is a great apartment.
我刚去过浴室 两边墙上都有镜子
In the bathroom there's mirrors on both sides of you.
尿尿的时候 就好像跟火箭女郎舞蹈团（一排人做同一个动作）一起尿尿
When you're in there,it's like peeing with the Rockettes.
我的梦想实现了
Well,there's my fantasy come true.
不，说真的
Seriously.
我们正在赞美你的公寓，老兄
We were just saying,great apartment!
谢了，你要吗？
Thanks. You want it?
我要搬去一个更大的
I'm moving to a bigger place.
你真的应该租下来
You should take this one.
你看我会住这种地方吗？
Can you see me in a place like this?
有何不可呢？你讨厌公园景观 跟高天花板吗？
Why not? You hate park views and high ceilings?
来吧，我带你去看厨房
Come on,I'll show you the kitchen.
不用了，兄弟 我今早在电视上…
That's all right,I saw a kitchen this morning.
…看过一个厨房
On TV.
不要再说了
Stop talking. Okay!
来嘛，告诉我们 对，她真只有二十？
-Come on,tell us! -ls she really 20?
你们休想逼我说什么
I am not telling you guys anything.
来嘛，理查，今天是我生日 让我也感同深受一下嘛
Come on,it's my birthday. Let me live vicariously!
爸，你真的不会想那样做
Dad,you really don't want to do that.
跟朋友分享一下 你的中年危机嘛
What's a little midlife crisis between friends?
杰克，你别说了，好吗？
Would you let it go?
我了解你在做什么 我五十时买了部保时捷
I know what you're going through. When I turned 50,I got the Porsche.
你有自己的小“加速器”
You got your own little speedster.
各位，说真的，不是像那样 这样吧
-Seriously,it's not like that. -Tell you what.
或许找个周末 我把车子借给你，而你的小…
Maybe one of these weekends you can borrow the car and I could
爸，我求你不要说完那个句子
Dad,I beg you not to finish that sentence!
怎么？我在逗他
What? I'm kidding!
我才不会让他碰我的保时捷
You know I'd never let him touch the Porsche.
瑞秋
Okay,Rach.
哪一朵百合？ 这一朵或那一朵？
Which lily? This lily or that lily?
我… 我喜欢这朵
-Well,l -I like this lily.
开得比较大，就像我妈
It's more open and that's like my mom.
她有比较开放给予的精神
She had a more open,giving spirit.
来亨鸡福亨（华纳动画中的搞笑公鸡）
Foghorn Leghorn!
金发女孩，你去第二间
Blonde girl? You're in room two.
没那么金的，你跟我来
Not-so-blonde girl,you're with me.
走吧
Here we go!
你不进去？
You're not going.
怎么了？是因为罗斯的话吗？
Is this because of what Ross said?
是啦，或许 我真不敢相信
-Well,yeah,maybe. -I don't believe this.
你们的关系这样维持吗？ 罗斯是老板？
Is this how this relationship works? Ross equals boss?
拜托 现在是1922年吗？
Come on,what is this,1922?
1922年有什么？
What's 1922?
只是很久以前嘛
Just,you know,a long time ago.
当时是男人命令女人做事的时代
When men used to tell women what to do a lot.
然后还有投票权 那是件好事，但听起来很可怕
Then there was suffrage,which was a good thing. But it sounds horrible.
你到底要不要刺？
Do you want this tattoo?
我要啊，只是罗斯他…
Yes,I do. It's just that Ross
你男友是你的老板吗？
Is your boyfriend the boss of you?
那好，谁是你的老板？
Who is the boss of you?
你？
You?
不，你是你的老板
You are the boss of you!
你现在给我进去 把那颗红心刺上去
You march in there and get that heart tattoo on your hip!
去
Go!
我甚至还没刺我的，我仍然很坚强
I haven't even gotten my tattoo and I'm already tougher.
你怎么了？
How you doing?
我是个年幼女友
I'm a twinkie!
真的？我是英雄
Really? I'm a hero.
这好难哦
This is so hard.
是呀，我知道，我也讨厌这样
Yeah,I know. I hate it too.
听着，或许我们应该说出来
Look,maybe we should just tell them.
或许我们应该先告诉你父母
Maybe we should just tell your parents first.
我父母死了
My parents are dead.
你真幸运
God,you are so lucky!
不，我是说… 你懂我意思
I mean Well,you know what I mean.
忍耐一下，好吗？
Just hang in there,okay?
我先出去，好吗？
Okay,I'll go out first,all right?
茱蒂，上洗手间呀，干得好
Judy! Going to the bathroom. Good for you!
谢谢，理查，很感激你的支持
Thank you,Richard. I appreciate the support.
亲爱的
Honey.
你有没有看到我的哈蒙奇欧球棒 鲍勃不相信我有
Seen my Harmon Kille brew bat? Bob doesn't believe I have one.
我不知道
I have no idea.
你知道 理查在城里有个年幼女友吗？
Did you know Richard has a twinkie in the city?
我知道，他像个全新的男人，好像电影《魔茧》里的情节一样 （一群养老院的老人因为一个天外来客而变得重新年轻）
I know. He's a new man. It's like a scene from Cocoon.
我无法想象理查跟一个行为不检点的女人在一起
I just never would have pictured Richard with a bimbo.
显然他告诉强尼 那个女孩不错
He told Johnny Shapiro that she's quite a girl.
事实上，他告诉强尼 他想他爱上她了
He told Johnny that he thinks he's falling in love with her.
真的？ 告诉你，我没见他这么快乐过
-Really? -I've never seen him this happy.
杰克…
So,Jack...
…你有没有想过 拿我去换个年轻模特？
...ever think about trading me in for a younger model?
当然没有
Of course not.
你不就等于两个25岁的佳人吗？
With you,it's like I've got two 25-year-olds.
杰克，住手
Oh,Jack,stop!
来嘛
Come on!
今天是我生日
It's my birthday!
别说了，好吗？
Can we drop this?
我对那家伙的公寓没兴趣
I am not interested in the guy's apartment.
拜托，我看到你 检查他房子装饰的样子
Oh,please. I saw the way you were checking out his moldings.
你想要
You want it.
我干嘛要另外一个房子？
Why would I want another apartment?
我已经有个我爱的房子了
I've already got an apartment that I love.
是嘛，偶尔这样说说又不会死
It wouldn't kill you to say it once in a while.
好吧，想听实话吗？ 我的确在考虑
All right. You want the truth? I'm thinking about it.
什么？ 抱歉
-What? -I'm sorry.
我今年28了 从没自己住过…
I'm 28. I've never lived alone...
…而我终于赚到足够的钱…
...and I'm at a place where I got enough money...
…可以让我不再需要室友
...that I don't need a roommate.
我也不需要室友啊
I don't need a roommate either.
自己住这里我也负担得起
I can afford to live here by myself.
我或许一个礼拜 得请一次人来舔我的银餐具
I may have to bring in somebody once a week to lick the silverware.
你火气干嘛那么大
Why are you getting so bent out of shape?
我们又没说要永远住在一起
We didn't agree to live together forever.
我们又不是伯特和厄尼（《芝麻街》中住在一起的动画角色）
We're not Bert and Ernie.
我意识到我们不是同志恋人，好吗
I' m aware that we' re not gay puppets, all right?
知道吗？
You know what?
如果你这样觉得…
If this is the way you feel...
…那或许你应该搬去
...then maybe you should take it.
我是那样觉得 那或许你应该搬去
-That's how I feel. -Then maybe you should take it!
那或许我会
Maybe I will!
无所谓 很好
-Fine with me! -Great!
你就有多点时间 跟你真正的朋友…
You can spend more quality time with your real friends...
…你的汤匙 在一起了
...the spoons!
谁还要再喝点？
Whose drink can I freshen?
快要切蛋糕了
Almost time for cake!
莫妮卡？你还好吗？
Mon,are you okay?
记得我发现 爸妈的那卷录影带吗？
You remember that video I found of Mom and Dad?
我刚看了现场秀
Well,I just caught the live show.
嗨 怎样？
-Hey,there. -What?
没什么 我刚听到你的好话
Nothing. I just heard something nice about you.
真的？
Really?
你儿子现在没女朋友吧？ 据我所知，没有
-Your son isn't seeing anyone,is he? -Not that I know of.
我是在想… 他何不打个电话给莫妮卡？
I was thinking,why doesn't he give Monica a call?
那…是个主意
That's an idea.
事实上，我已经有男友了
Well,actually,I'm already seeing someone.
是吗？
Oh?
这孩子什么事都不讲
She never tells us anything.
罗斯 你知道莫妮卡有男友了吗？
Ross,did you know Monica's seeing someone?
妈，我周遭有好多好多人
Mom,there are so many people in my life.
有些人有男朋友，有些人没有
Some are seeing people and some aren't.
那是玻璃的吗？
Is that crystal?
那个神秘男子是谁？
So who's the mystery man?
他是个医生（跟“博士”同词）
Well,he's a doctor.
真正的医生？
A real doctor?
不，他是研究肉的
No,a doctor of meat.
他当然是真的医生
Of course he's a real doctor.
他很英俊
And he's handsome.
人很好 我知道你会喜欢他
And he's sweet,and I know you'd like him.
那太棒了
Well,that's wonderful.
妈，没关系
Mom,it's okay.
没错，茱蒂
It is,Judy.
杰克
Jack!
请你进来一下，好吗？
Could you come in here for a moment?
现在
Now!
找到了 交给我，爸
-Found it! -I'll take that,Dad.
你女儿跟理查看来似乎是一对
It seems your daughter and Richard are something of an item.
那不可能，他在城里有个年幼女友
That's impossible. He's got a twinkie in the city.
爸，我是那个年幼女友
I'm the twinkie.
你是那个年幼女友？ 她不年幼
-You're the twinkie? -She's not a twinkie!
好吧，听着，各位 这是我有过最棒的关系…
Look,this is the best relationship I've been in
拜托，关系？
Oh,please! A relationship?
对，关系
Yes,a relationship!
你们请听好 我为这个男人疯狂
For your information,I'm crazy about this man.
真的？
Really?
我生日还要站在这里 听你说这些鬼话吗？
Am I supposed to stand here and listen to this on my birthday?
这是件好事，你自己也说 你没见理查那么快乐过
This is a good thing. You said you've never seen Richard happier.
我何时说的？
When did I say that?
楼上的卫生间啊，在你摸妈之前
Upstairs in the bathroom,right before you felt up Mom!
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快乐，杰克
Happy birthday,dear Jack
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you
好漂亮哦，我好喜欢
It looks so good! Oh,I love it.
我知道，我也是 菲比，我好高兴你逼我刺
I know,so do l! I'm so glad you made me do this.
让我看你的
Okay,let me see yours.
再瞧瞧你的
Let's see yours again.
菲比，我的才刚看过 让我看你的
We just saw mine. Let me see yours.
不…
Oh,no!
不见了，好古怪哦
It's gone! That's so weird.
不知道去哪里了
I don't know how,where it went.
-你没刺？ -是的
-You didn't get it?-No
你为什么没刺？
Why not?
对不起…
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
菲比，你怎么可以这样对我？ 这全是你的主意
How could you do this to me? This was your idea!
我知道…我本来是要刺的 可是他拿着针走进来
I know! I was gonna get it,but he came in with this needle.
你知道他们是用针刺的吗？
And did you know they do this with needles?
真的？真想不到？
Really? You don't say?
因为我的是猫舔上去的
Because mine was licked on by kittens!
真对不起，说真的，疼吗？
I'm sorry.Seriously, does it hurt a lot?
不，只是一点痛，就像
No, it's just a pinch. Like that--
上帝啊
Oh, my God!
弄疼我了，哦，肯定会留下一个疤的
That really hurt me!Oh, that's gonna leave a mark.
听着，今天的事我很抱歉…
I'm sorry about what
我也是 我知道
-Yeah,me too. -I know.
我们需要抱一下吗？
Do we need to hug?
不，没关系
No,we're all right.
我有东西送你
So I got you something.
塑料汤匙
Plastic spoons!
太棒了 舔吧，老兄
-Great! -Lick away,my man!
这在我的新家会很实用 在我买到真的之前
These will go great in my new place till I get real ones.
什么？
What?
我不能永远用塑料汤匙 这不环保
I can't use these forever. They're no friend of the environment.
不…我是说… 你说什么新家？
No,I mean what's this about your new place?
我要搬出去，像我们谈过的
I'm moving out,like we talked about.
我不知道你是认真的
I didn't think that was serious.
我以为我们只是在吵架
You know,I thought that was just a fight.
我们是吵架了…
Well,it was a fight...
…有根据的，记得吗？
... based on serious stuff,remember?
关于我从没一个人住过
About how I never lived alone or anything?
我只是想，这对我有好处 帮我成长…
I think it would be good for me. Help me to grow...
…之类的
...or whatever.
好，你去吧
Well,there you go.
你没问题吗？
Hey,are you cool with this?
我不想让你又高又干（孤立无援）
I don't wanna leave you high and dry.
不，我从来没有又低又湿
I've never been lower or wetter.
我不要紧的 我就把你的房间…
I'll be fine. I'll just turn your...
…改成游戏室之类的好了
... bedroom into a game room.
把足球桌放在里面
Put the foosball table in there.
那桌子为什么该归你？
Why do you get to keep the table?
我付了一半的钱
I did pay for half of it.
对，我付了另一半
I paid for the other half.
这样吧，谁赢谁的
I'll tell you what. I'll play you for it.
好呀，没问题
All right,you're on.
我可以抽出2分钟时间来痛宰你一顿
I can take two minutes out of my day to kick your ass.
我得的分 会比你妹被上过的次数还多
Your men will get scored on more times than your sister.
哪一个妹妹？
Which sister?
你后悔我告诉他们吗？
So are you sorry that I told them?
不，我跟你爸好久没去跑步了
No. It's been a long time since your dad and I went running.
你们刺了吗？给我看
Did you get it?
罗斯在吗？ 不在，他去买披萨
-ls Ross here? -He went out for pizza.
好的，快点看
Okay,really quick.
好漂亮
That's great!
很有品味
Very tasteful.
要看我的吗？…
Wanna see mine? Wanna see mine?
什么？你又没刺
What? You didn't get one.
那这是什么？
Okay. Well then,what is this?
我们在看什么？
What are we looking at?
那颗蓝雀斑？
That blue freckle?
那是我的刺青
That's my tattoo.
那不是刺青，那什么也不是
That is not a tattoo. That is a nothing.
我终于逼她回去再刺…
I got her in the chair...
…针根本都还没碰到她 她就跳起来尖叫逃走
...he barely touched her with the needle,she screamed and that was it.
嗨
Okay,hi!
其实告诉你吧，这正是我想要的
For your information,this is exactly what I wanted.
这个刺青是从很远很远的地方看到的地球
This is a tattoo of the Earth as seen from a great,great distance.
我妈从天堂看到我就是这样的
It's the way my mother sees me from heaven.
真是狗屁一堆
Oh,what a load of crap!
那是一个点
That is a dot!
你妈正在天堂上大叫 “我的百合在哪里？你这个懦弱的人”
Your mother's in heaven going,"Where the hell's my lily,you wuss!"
菲比，那不是个刺青 这才是个刺青
That is not a tattoo! This is a tattoo!
你去刺青了？
You got a tattoo?
或许
Maybe.
只是个小的啦 菲比刺了整个地球
But just a little one. Phoebe got the whole world!
让我看看
Well,let me see.
怎样？
Well?
这非常的…
Well,it's really...
性感
...sexy.
我没想到会这样，但…
I wouldn't have thought it would be,but...
…哇
...wow!
真的？
Really?
对，会酸痛吗？ 你可以活动吗？
So is it sore? Or can you do stuff?
可以吧
I guess.
留些披萨给我们
Save us some pizza.
别窝在角落
Get it out of the corner!
传球…
Pass it! Pass it!
别跟你的人讲话
Stop talking to your men!
太好了，桌子是我的了
And the table is mine.
恭喜了
Congratulations.
你们还是会来看我，对吧？
You guys will still come visit me,right?
会呀，你有大屏幕电视
Oh,yeah! You got the big TV.
我们会常常去的
We'll be over there all the time.
除了在这里时
Except when we are here.
我知道你只是往上城区搬 我还是会很想你的
I know you're just moving uptown,but I'll really miss you.
你怎会不再是我的对门了？
How can you not be across the hall anymore?
是呀，谁来吃光我们的东西 占用我们的电话…
Who's gonna eat all of our food and tie up our phone lines
那是我的胸罩吗？
Is that my bra?
你拿我的胸罩去干嘛？ 不…不是你想的那样
-What are you doing with my bra? -It's not what you think.
我们用那个来在屋顶上弹水球
We used it to fling water balloons off the roof.
记得吗？那些初中生 连弹到对面都办不到
Remember? Those kids couldn't even get theirs across the street.
是呀，我记得
Yeah,I remember.
咱们把剩下的搬上卡车
Let's bring the rest of these down to the truck.
你要我…
You want me to...
…帮你搬这个足球桌下去吗？
...give you a hand with the foosball table?
不了，你留着，你需要练习
You keep it. You need the practice.
谢了
Thanks.
那么…
So...
…我猜就这样了
... I guess this is it.
是呀，对
Yeah,right.
大概吧
I guess so.
我不知道我们何时会再见？
When am I gonna see you?
我猜今晚在咖啡馆？
I'm guessing tonight at the coffeehouse.
对呀
Right. Yeah. Okay.
保重了
Take care.
-嘿，爸爸，你怎么来了 -我只是顺便拜访你的男友，有些事情
-Hey, Dad. What are you doing here?.-I just stopped by your boyfriend's to get a piece of my mind
-然后呢？-我在他的鼻子上打了一拳
-And?.-I was gonna punch him in the nose.
但是他开始看比赛，所以我们一起看
But he had the game on,so we started watching.
在中场阶段，我才想起来要干嘛
At halftime,I was gonna give him what for.
-但是他给了我一瓶啤酒，知道什么吗？-什么？
-But he offered me a beer. Know what?.-What?.
他打开了音响
He's got on tap!
为什么在他的公寓里，每件东西都恰好放在那里，真是不敢相信
when he in this apartment, the damn thing is build right on his part. It's unbelievable!
你们谈到我了吗
Dad, did you talk about me?.
哦，对了，其实，我们没有谈到你
Oh, right. Well, actually,we never got to you.
你已经是个大姑娘了，我只希望你知道自己在做什么
Look, you're a big girl. I just hope you know what you're doing.
我知道
I do.
-你系了我给你买的领带 -是的
-You're wearing the tie I got you!-Yeah.
帽子哪来的
So where did you get the hat?.
不知道
I don't know.